So shout out to the Alphabet Boys podcast because they uncovered that this broad right here is an op.
So this is Chelsea, or at least that's the fake name that she assumed when she infiltrated the Colorado chapter of Black Lives Matter and tried her best to get everybody to commit gun crimes.
She was all up in the protest and she was like, yeah, you should try this.
You should do this.
And thankfully, folks was like, nah, I'm good.
Thank you, Motto.
Appreciate you.
A whole operative.
She is still employed by the Colorado Springs police and was sent here with a fake name and a whole fake identity that she was a sex worker who had been harmed by police.
And that's why she was here in solidarity.
Now, we all know that these law enforcement agencies, the FBI, the CIA, the police have had a long storied history of infiltrating social justice movements and trying to turn us against each other and trying to trick people.
Entrapment into committing crimes, don't fall for it.
Keep your head on swivel and ultimately don't trust anybody that just pops up like I'm down and doesn't have references and a history that you can track of actually being down.
Not even the black folks.
Rest in peace, Fred Hampton.